(Get ready, wake your psyche up, MOB!)
(Get ready, dig your anger up, MOB!)
(Get ready!)
Coming down, could you fill your satisfaction?
You're a MOB. Can't you feel your own frustration?
You're a MOB. What do you want to be?
Wear your overflowing emotions on your sleeve and break it down.
What do you see once you go beyond your limits?
(99.9! 99.9!)
The mysterious percentage.
Cryin' my life, cryin' my psyche,
cryin' my heart in such commonplaces!
Is that your ideal? Is that your mind?
It all begins when it hits 100.
The MOB is alive. The MOB is high.
The MOB is staying frustrated, aren't you?
Is that your ideal? Is that your mind? Right now...
Your life is your own.
(Get ready, wake your psyche up, MOB!)
Mob Psycho
(Get ready, dig your anger up, MOB!)
(Get ready, wake your psyche up, MOB!)
(Get ready!)
Boss Fight
~The Final Light~
Now I'll be able to hit
you with everything...
（モブ）
これで思う存分ぶつけられる
My powers... and my rage.
この“力”
この怒りを！
Output 20%
Is that it?
（鈴木(すずき)）
終わりか？
This is finally getting interesting.
面白くなってきたじゃないか
お前も…
You're...
You're enjoying this too, aren't you?
お前も楽しんでいるのだな
What the hell is going on?
（誇山(こやま)）
何が起きてんだ？
（星野武史(ほしのたけし)）
規模が違い過ぎて…
They're fighting in
a whole different stratosphere!
As righteous as you try to sound,
deep down, you're the same as me.
どんなにきれい事を言ったところで
やはり本質は私と同じ
Nii-san!
（影山(かげやま) 律(りつ)）
兄さん！
How does it feel to be released
from your shackles?
（鈴木）
解き放たれた気分はどうだ？
We are freer than anyone else!
我々は誰よりも自由！
ぶはっ
（律）
兄さん…
Nii-san...
ああ 僕は…
How... How could I...
僕は なんて愚かなヤツなんだ
How could I be so foolish?
It may have only been for a moment,
but I let this power control me!
ほんの一瞬でも この暴れる力に
流されてしまうなんて
You're so emotionally unstable.
情緒不安定なヤツめ
At this rate, you'll never catch up to me,
no matter how far you go.
そんな様子では どこまで行っても
お前は私までたどりつけまい
I am the best in the world!
私が世界一だ！
How did your life end up being so hollow?
（モブ）
どうして あんたの人生は
そんなにむなしいものに
なってしまったんだろう
I can't judge you for the life
you chose, though.
でも 僕には
その生き方を責めることができない
You were just unlucky.
あんたは運が悪かったんだ
ふん 何を言ってる
What are you talking about?
There is no one in this world
that is as lucky as me!
私ほど運に恵まれた者は
ほかにいないだろう！
Output 50%
Heaven bestowed these powers upon me
天が与えたこの“力”
and made you all extras,
created solely to make my star shine!
お前たちは世界の主役である私を
引き立てる端役にすぎない
Really? Then it wasn't luck
that you were lacking.
（モブ）
そうか
だったら 足りなかったのは
運じゃない
縁だ
It was bonds.
なに？
What?
You were the only one
who existed in your world.
あんたの世界には
あんた１人しか いなかったんだ
圧倒的に孤独な人間
You lived in overwhelming solitude.
僕にも分かる
思い出したくもない孤独な世界
I know that feeling well...
Living in a world where I'm completely alone,
one I want to forget forever.
I don't understand.
分からないな
Why?
なぜ泣く必要がある？
Why are you crying?
You might not believe me,
（モブ）
信じてもらえないかもしれないけど
but I really don't want to hurt you.
本当は
あんたも傷つけたくないんだ
ごめん
I'm sorry...
What the hell is going on?
（霊幻新隆(れいげんあらたか)）
何が どうなってんだ？
（エクボ）
俺様に聞くな
Don't ask me.
（芹沢(せりざわ)）
社長の気配が なくなった
The president's aura is gone.
Does that mean it's over?
（桜威(さくらい)）
決着がついたということか？
おお やった！
Yes!
Impressive. Is that boy actually human?
（嶽内(たけうち)）
さすがだ　あの少年は人間なのか？
He's just a normal middle school kid.
（テル）
彼は普通の中学生ですよ
Nii-san... You used a tremendous
amount of power again.
（律）
兄さん
また随分 大きな力を使ったね
It's not over yet.
（ショウ）
まだだ
My dad's aura didn't disappear.
おやじの気配は消えたんじゃねえ
It changed.
変わったんだ
My dad mentioned before that
he picked up the habit of only awakening
おやじは言ってた
後天的に覚醒するきっかけは
過度のストレスだって
when put under a lot of stress.
（衝突音）
（モブ）がはっ
（鈴木）
うりゃ～
（槌屋(つちや)）
人知を超えてるね
This goes beyond human understanding.
How can one man's powers be so immense?
（邑機(むらき)）
個の力が
ここまで大きくなりうるとは
（エクボ）
茂夫(しげお)
Shigeo... This is the one day in your life
you shouldn't try to do the impossible.
今日ばかりは
無理を通そうとすんなよ
He's already using way more power
than he did when beat me.
（テル）
僕を負かしたときの力は
とっくに出てるはずなのに
If you can't win, run.
（霊幻）
勝てなければ逃げろ
You're not responsible for any of this,
お前が背負ってる責任なんか
何もないんだぞ モブ
Mob.
（鈴木）
ハア～
I've never felt like this before.
かつてない気分だ
Wake up.
起きろ
Don't think I'm going to let you say
you're done already.
こんなに早く終わらせることは
許さんぞ
Wake up!
起きろ！
No.
（モブ）
ダメだ
As much as I hate to admit it,
（モブ）
悔しいけど 僕じゃ力不足だ
I'm not strong enough.
I don't have the power to show you a new path.
何か別の道を
あんたに示すほどの力はない
お前には私の破壊衝動につきあう
義務があるんだぞ！
You awakened my destructive impulses,
now you have to deal with them!
今更 殻に籠もってどうする！
Don't go hiding in your shell now!
I give up.
（モブ）
諦めた
I hoped that you could turn over a new leaf
and become a better person,
あんたが
いい人に変わる希望は―
もう 捨てた
but that hope's gone now!
（鈴木）
ぐわっ！
ど… どうやら…
I-It appears... that we're both...
我々は互いに大き… な…
influencing each other quite a bit...
影響を受けているようだな
Yes. But I couldn't be a good influence.
でも いい影響は与えられなかった
I'm done. We can both lose at this point.
もういい　お互い 負けでいい
ぐわっ
Output 100%
This is...
（モブ）
怖っ…
死んじゃうかも
I might actually die...
（霊幻）
モブ！
Mob!
茂夫
Shigeo.
Nii-san!
（律）兄さん
（テル）やあ
Heya.
よくやった
Well done.
（モブ）
なんてことはない
No, this is nothing.
Nothing compared to the fear
of losing all I have.
失う怖さに比べれば…
Body improvement! Fight on!
（モブ）
肉改～！
ファイ オ～！
（鈴木）
ぐおっ
がはっ
（モブ）
倒す！
I'll defeat you!
（鈴木）
ぐわ… ぐぐ…
ぐわ～！
（モブ）
あんなものが外に出てきたら
If something like that makes it outside...
爆発…
It'll explode...
え？　爆発する？
It'll explode?
Oh, it'll explode!
あっ 爆発する！
Run away! Everyone, run away!
逃げて みんな！
逃げて！
Mob!
（霊幻）モブ！
（エクボ）生きてたか！
You're alive!
He ended up releasing too much
energy and self-destructed!
（モブ）
あの人は力を出し過ぎて
自滅しました
You're bleeding like crazy!
大出血じゃねえか！
（モブ）
師匠 逃げてください！
Master, please run!
All that's left is an
excessive amount of energy.
残ったのは膨大なエネルギー
I'm pretty sure an explosion will happen,
多分 爆発が起きます
a huge one at that!
それも 大爆発が！
So you're saying we won't
be able to contain it.
僕らじゃ防げないってことだね
急ごう！
Let's hurry!
おう 律
Ritsu.
Let's run. We're gonna get caught
up in that if we stay here.
走ろうぜ
ここじゃ 巻き込まれちまう
That's the president's final light...
（芹沢）
あれは社長の最期の光だ
Our president who was trying
to take over the world...
世界征服を目指した社長の…
（羽鳥(はとり)）
いいから走れ！　死ぬぞ！
Just shut up and run! You're gonna die!
Huh? Hey, where's Shigeo?
あれ？
おい 茂夫は どこ行った？
You made the right choice.
（鈴木）
お前の判断は正しい
There's no way to avoid this.
回避は間に合わん
Your only choice is to end my life—
to sever the energy source—
爆発を起こす前に
エネルギーの発生源である
私の命を絶つしか…
before the explosion happens.
何をしている？
What are you doing?
I'm going to contain the explosion.
（モブ）
爆発を止める
In the end, you aren't able to defeat me,
（鈴木）
結局 お前は私を倒すことも
仲間を助けることも
save your friends, or save yourself.
自らも守ることも できないのだな
With your powers, you should've
been able to handle this better.
お前の力なら
もっとうまくやれたはずだ
Just having powers doesn't mean
everything works out for you.
力を持ってるだけじゃ
うまくいかないよ
But that's perfectly fine,
でも それでいいんだ
as long as you make
the important choices yourself.
大事な部分を
自分で選んで生きてさえいれば
I'm the protagonist of my own life.
僕の人生の主役は僕だから
That's why I chose to be here.
（モブ）
だから 自分で選んでここに来た
No matter how much I dislike you,
to leave you to suffer on your own
いくら嫌いな相手でも
たった独りで苦しんでいるなんて
would just be too sad.
やっぱり かわいそうだし
だから 助ける
So I'm going to help you.
What do you plan to do with that filthy cat?
（鈴木）
そんな汚い猫を拾ってきて
どうする気だ？
Well, the poor thing was drenched
and shivering in the rain.
（鈴木の妻）
だって 雨の中震えてて
かわいそうなんだもの
And think about it...
それに ほら
きっとショウも優しい子になるわ
Sho will grow up into a gentle boy.
He's going to grow up watching you, after all.
あなたを見て育つんだからね
優しく 優しくよ
We need to be gentle. Gentle.
どうして
あんな乱暴なやり方をしたの？
Why did you have to be so violent?!
（鈴木）
組織を統制するには 圧倒的な力を
見せつけてやったほうがいい
To lead an organization,
I need to establish my dominance.
You can't move people's hearts
with psychic powers!
超能力じゃ 人の心は動かせない
No, power is absolute.
いや “力”は絶対だ
As long as I have this power,
people will follow me.
この“力”があれば
人は ついてくる
You think that's true for everyone?
誰でも？　そう思うの？
I do.
Sho is also showing interest
in my powers as well.
ショウも私の“力”に
憧れを抱いてい…
Goodbye.
（妻）
さよなら
When did I...
（鈴木）
私は いつか…
ぐう… 吸収すれば…
If I can absorb it...
Don't. You'll just end up...
（鈴木）
よせ！　これでは お前が！
（モブ）
がああ～！
You wanted to apologize, didn't you?!
（モブ）
謝りたかったんでしょ？
Then you need to do it say it loud and clear!
だったら ちゃんと
伝えなきゃダメだよ
That's right. I also...
そうだ 僕だって…
I also have someone I need
to express my feelings to!
僕だって
気持ちを伝えたい人がいるんだ！
Mob...
（霊幻）
モブ…
Mob Psycho
Nii-san!
（律）
兄さん！
Hey, wake up!
（エクボ）
おい 起きろ！
Kageyama-kun!
（テル）影山君
（霊幻）モブ
Mob!
（エクボ）
茂夫！
Shigeo!
兄さん！
Nii-san!
He's regained consciousness.
意識が戻った
Let's dig him out.
掘り起こしましょう
Thank goodness you're okay.
（テル）
無事でよかったよ
Unbelievable.
（霊幻）
たまげたな
Anyway, we should get away from here.
とにかく
ここを離れたほうが よさそうだ
歩けるか？
Can you walk?
Yes...
（モブ）
はい
みんな ケガが治ってるんだよ
All of our wounds have been healed.
Our clothes are in shambles, though.
服はボロボロだけど
あっ ホントだ
You're right...
Shigeo, what's up with
the left side of your chest?
茂夫 その左胸どうした？
That's quite the bold fashion statement.
（エクボ）
えらく強気なファッションだな
まったく 君は
いつも僕の想像を超えてくるな
Seriously... You never cease to amaze.
I do consider you my rival, you know?
これでもライバルだと思ってるんだ
Don't wander off too far.
あまり遠い存在にならないでくれよ
This ground... It's not concrete.
（モブ）
この地面 コンクリートじゃない
My mind feels all spacey.
頭がボ～ッとする
The sky seems cramped.
空が狭い
Where are we?
ここは どこだろう？
（霊幻）
出口だ　落下物に気をつけろよ
There's the exit. Watch out for
things that may fall onto your head.
It's quiet.
（テル）
静かだ
Surprisingly, there aren't any
news helicopters flying around.
報道ヘリとか飛んでないんですね
意外と
（霊幻）
そりゃ そうだ
Well, yeah.
They're too scared to come here
when they know so little.
不用意に近づくには
得体が知れな過ぎる
Everything seems fine,
even after that giant explosion.
（モブ）
大爆発にしては無事だけど
どういうこと？
What's going on?
I seriously thought
you were a goner back there.
（霊幻）
お前 あのときは
もうダメかと思ったぞ
I was sure ground zero
would've been eviscerated.
爆心地は絶望的な状況だろうと
The hell is that?
何だ ありゃ？
But what appeared there happened to be...
だが そこに現れたのは…
あっ おい！
Hey!
（律）
兄さん！
Nii-san!
Are you okay?
Are you still actually hurt somewhere?
大丈夫？　もしかして
どこか痛めたままなんじゃ？
Thanks, Ritsu. I think my body's okay.
ありがとう 律
体は無事なんだけど
But lately, whenever I use a lot of power,
最近 大きな“力”を使ったあとは
起きてられなかったりするんだ
I have a hard time staying awake afterward.
Huh?
I'll carry you partway,
途中まで僕が運ぶから
寝てていいよ
so you can rest.
Carry him where? Our house is...
でも 運ぶっていっても家は…
Sorry, he'll fix up your house,
but he'll need three days.
悪(わり)い　全焼した家の修復は
こいつがするから
３日ほど待っててくれ
Just three days?!
（東尾(ひがしお)）
３日って…
You guys wanna come to my place?
（霊幻）
お前ら 俺んち来るか？
It'll be a bit cramped,
but I'm sure we can make it work.
ちょっと狭いけど
なんとかなるだろう
At least try to hide your displeasure, jeez.
露骨に嫌そうな顔すんなよ！
Oh, don't worry about me.
僕は大丈夫です
Could we stop by the school first?
（律）
その前に
学校 寄ってもいいですか？
At this hour?
（霊幻）
こんな時間にか？
There should be a spare
tracksuit in his club room.
（律）
部室に替えのジャージが
あるはずなので
Telepathy Club
Body Improvement Club
That must be it.
（霊幻）
あれか
I wonder if I could borrow one for myself.
（律）
ほかの部員のジャージも
僕用に借りていいかな？
Body improvement
Lower body
strengthening month!!
But I can't do it without asking...
いや でも 無断は…
Tracksuit thieves!
（郷田武蔵(ごうだむさし)）
ジャージ泥棒～！
（モブ）
あ… 部長
Captain.
My heart just stopped!
（霊幻）
心臓 止まった
I see.
（郷田）
なるほどな
I came here to get some dumbbells,
and you sure gave me a scare.
いや～ ダンベルを
取りに来たところだったが
ビックリしたぞ
Sorry... You scared us pretty good, too.
すみません
こちらも驚きました
Put on the muscle! Burn the fat!
I understand the situation now.
事情は分かった
ちょっと待っててくれ
Hang on one second.
あ～ もしもし 実は…
Hello? You see...
Um... Why's everyone from
the Body Improvement Club here?
いや どうして肉改部の皆さんが
集まってるんでしょうか？
We're about to...
僕たちは これから…
The Body Improvement Club
これより肉体改造部
３泊４日の強化トレーニング
地獄合宿を開催する！
will now begin a three-day four-night
strengthening hell training camp!
No, we're—
いや 僕たちは…
We should always help
each other out when in need!
困ったときこそ 助け合いだろう？
I mean, we're really tired—
いや 本当に疲れてまして…
ああ 広い布団で寝たほうが
いいだろう？
I'm sure you want to sleep on a giant futon!
No, a small one will do just fine!
別に狭くてもいいので
俺のばあちゃんちなら
みんなを泊められるぞ
We have enough room for all
of you at my granny's house!
You have to procure and make your own food,
so it'll be excellent training!
食べ物も自給自足で
いいトレーニングになる
90分もジョギングすれば すぐ着く
さあ 行こう！
And it's just a 90-minute jog away!
We'll be there in no time!
Now, let's go!
R-Reigen-san, help...
れ… 霊幻さん 助け…
Hey, that's great. Do your best.
よかったな　頑張れよ お前ら
I'm gonna take a cab home.
俺はタクシーで帰るわ
Body Improvement!
（郷田）
肉改～！
Fight on! Fight on!
（部員たち）
ファイ オ～！　ファイ オ～！
How cruel...
（エクボ）
むごい…
I totally forgot!
忘れてた
I should've just gone over
to Reigen-san's place.
霊幻さんち
泊めてもらえばよかった
I wonder what that thing is.
（猿田(さるた)）
何なんすかね これ？
It's even more confusing up close.
（雉子林(きじばやし)）
近くで見ると
改めて 訳 分かんねえな
How do one of these things even grow?
（犬川(いぬかわ)）
何がどうなったら
こんな物が出来るんですかね？
Isn't it obvious?!
（暗田(くらた)トメ）
そんなの決まってるでしょ！
Aliens! This is the work of aliens!
宇宙人よ　宇宙人！
（信者たち）
おお！　すごい！
Amazing.
Could this be...
（信者）
これは もしや 教祖様の御業(みわざ)では？
The work of our beloved leader?
Wow... It looks like a vegetable.
（ツボミ）
すごっ　野菜みたい
（米里(めざと)イチ）
絶対 モブ君関係よね これ
I bet Mob-kun was involved.
I just know it.
（密裏賢治(みつうらけんじ)）
すごいじゃないか！
That's amazing!
You're the ones behind that giant plant?
あの巨大植物を君たちが？
ま… まあ
W-Well...
If you're asking if we were
directly involved, then no.
直接 俺たちが やったかっていうと
ちょっと違うけど
We basically were, though.
（朝日(あさひ) 豪(ごう)）
俺たちが やったようなもんだな
What?
Amazing! Fantastic!
（密裏）
すごいぞ　すごいぞ！
（黒崎(くろさき) 麗(れい)）
密裏さん
Mitsuura-san.
I think I'm going to stop coming here.
私 もうここに通うの
やめようと思います
Kurosaki-san? But why?!
黒崎さん どうして？
If everything goes well with your research
もし 密裏さんの研究が
うまくいって
and you actually develop the technology
to make espers out of people,
超能力の開発技術が
生まれてしまったら
we might get more espers
who misuse their powers.
また 力を悪用する人たちが
出てきてしまうかもしれないから
So I think you should just stop.
これ以上は
やめたほうがいいと思うの
I don't even need the money.
お小遣いも いりません
ぐはっ！
I agree.
（白鳥大地(しらとりだいち)）
それに賛成です
We're actually not that impressive.
（白鳥海斗(かいと)）
僕たちなんて大したことないのに
Kids...
君たち…
All right!
分かった
君たちを研究するのは
もうやめにしよう
I'll stop using you for research!
But to be honest, I'm just having fun
（密裏）
しかし 単純に楽しいんだ
spending time with you kids.
君たちと過ごすのが！
You don't mind coming by once
in a while as friends, do you?
たまに友人として
遊びに来てくれても いいだろ？
Hey. What are you going to do now?
（誇山）
お前 これからどうするんだ？
The organization is gone.
組織は もうないんだ
新しい生き方を探るしかないだろう
I'm obviously going to have
to find another way to live.
（誇山）
だよな
Yeah...
Now that the scars on my face are gone,
maybe I'll start up a ramen shop.
顔の傷もスッキリ消えたことだし
ラーメン屋でも やるか
The hospitality industry is not for you.
（桜威）
お前に客商売は無理だ
体力を生かせ
Just put your body to good use.
What are you going to do, Sakurai?
（誇山）
桜威は どうするんだ？
I have an interview at a convenience
store the day after tomorrow.
（桜威）
あさって コンビニの面接がある
What? You're going to ask him?
（槌屋）
え？　頼みに行く？
Yes. I'm considering asking Master Reigen
if I can study under him for a while.
（邑機）
ああ 霊幻先生のところで
お世話になろうかと
Don't. You're really not a people person.
やめときな
あんた 接客 向いてないよ
I agree. You're kinda dreary.
（無飼(むかい)）
僕もそう思う　ちょっと暗いもん
The government has determined that
（ヨシフ）
“政府は 一連の事件を―”
“空想に取りつかれた
犯罪集団による犯行と断定”か
this is the work of
a delusional criminal organization, huh?
I can't believe you turned yourself in
after being defeated by a civilian esper.
まさか 民間のエスパーに敗れて
出頭とはな
（鈴木）
事実だ
It's the truth.
ハア～ やれやれ
プロの立場がないな
Man, where does that leave us pros?
What's going to happen to my dad?
おやじは どうなる？
（ヨシフ）
う～ん 普通に考えれば
極刑は免れないだろうが
Under normal circumstances,
he'd be executed.
But there is a chance he'll be kept alive
as a research subject.
生かされて研究機関のモルモット
という可能性もあるだろう
Why'd he have to say that to his son?
（芹沢）
子供の前で
そんなことを言わなくたって…
Well, it's not my call to make,
（ヨシフ）
まあ 決めるのは俺じゃないし
どうなるかは分からないな
so I can't say for sure.
P-P-President!
（芹沢）
しゃ… 社長！
Serizawa.
（鈴木）
芹沢
I never actually considered
you all my comrades.
私は お前たちを心から仲間だとは
思っていなかったんだ
There's no reason to be worried about me.
気に病む必要はない
お前は自分に自信がない分
他人につけ込まれやすい
Because you lack self-confidence,
others will find you easy to manipulate.
Be careful from now on.
今後は気をつけるんだな
Sho.
ショウ
I wanted you to see your mother again,
お前には もう一度
母親に会わせてやりたかったが
but my pride severed that possibility.
私の傲慢が
つながりを引き裂いてしまった
I'm truly sorry.
本当にすまなかった
（ショウ）
いや たまに会ってるよ
母ちゃんなら
Don't be.
I see Mom every now and then.
She's always asking me how you're doing.
いつも おやじの近況なんか
聞きたがってさ
I wish I could've stopped you
before she found out what you'd become.
できれば 母ちゃんに
おやじの今を知られる前に
止めたかったけど
今朝 電話したら
今度 会いに行くってさ
When I called her this morning,
she said she'd come see you sometime.
So don't you dare think this is all over.
だから １人で勝手に
終わった気になるなよ
You still need to get an earful from Mom.
まだ母ちゃんに怒られる役目が
残ってんだからさ！
"People need other people," huh?
（鈴木）
“人には人が必要”か
Spirits and Such Consultation Office
What? It was just a short circuit?
え？　ただの漏電だったのかよ
（霊幻）
ネズミが配線かじったらしくてな
Apparently, a mouse bit into some wires.
おかげで火災保険も下りたし
新しい事務所で再スタートだな
Thanks to that, the fire insurance kicked in,
so we get a fresh start at a new office.
にしても まだ殺風景だな
But it sure looks bland right now.
Mob, do your thing.
モブ あれ やってくれ
Okay.
はい
Thanks.
助かったぜ
あっ 学ランの穴 思い出した
The hole in my uniform... I just remembered.
I'd put the broccoli seeds in there.
ポッケに入れてたの
ブロッコリーの種だ
Broccoli?
ブロッコリー？　あのときの種か
The seeds from back the—
なるほどな
Now I see.
あっ 師匠！　あれって…
Master, you mean that's...
Welp. Let's just forget we ever saw this.
（霊幻）
まあ 見なかったことにして
一旦 忘れよう
But man, he sure is late...
にしても 遅いな あいつ
（霊幻）
おお 来たか
Oh, there you are.
入れよ
Come in.
道に迷いました　申し訳ない
I got lost. I'm very sorry.
Thanks for the other day, Kageyama-kun.
影山君 先日はどうも
A suit...?
スーツ？
You're going to work here?
ここで働くんですか？
Yup. Reigen-san made me
an offer after all that.
うん あのあと
霊幻さんが誘ってくれたんだ
He said that there was something
that even I could do.
俺にもできることがあるって
And it's the least I can do after
my organization caused everyone trouble.
それに
組織が迷惑をかけたし
償いも兼ねて
We're here to make a better tomorrow,
so this is perfect for you!
うちは善良な社会作りに
貢献できるから ピッタリだぜ！
は… はい！　頑張ります！
Y-Yes, sir! I'll do my best!
もうじき依頼人が来る
My client will be here soon,
but before that...
その前にこれだな
Huh?
We're going to have to
do something about that.
そのままじゃ仕事にならん
Huh?
おおっ スゲえな
Whoa, that's amazing.
（霊幻）
ふむ
He looks so different.
変わった！
（霊幻）
まあ ひとまず
I guess he at least looks like
he can pull off customer service now.
客商売できる
身なりにはなったか
C-Customer service?! Wh-What should
I do when a customer shows up?!
きゃ… 客商売？
お… お客さんが来たら
俺は どう動けば？
What did you do at your last job?
前の会社では？
My orders were to smack them with
my umbrella if I sensed any hostility...
（芹沢）
とりあえず
敵意を感じたら
傘で殴れって
指示だったんで
The hell?
なんだ そりゃ？
Yeah, things aren't that different here.
あ～
うちも大体 同じ
If there's anything else
you don't understand,
あとは分からないことがあったら
先輩に聞いてくれ
go ahead and ask your senior there.
Senior?
先輩？
Mob, you show him the ropes
while he's still in training.
（霊幻）
モブ 研修期間が
終わるまで
いろいろ
教えてやってくれ
Huh?
It's a pleasure to work with you,
Kageyama-senpai!
よろしくお願いします 影山先輩！
Huh? It's... a pleasure
to work with you, too...
え？　あ…
よろしくお願いします
What should I do?
Now I'm getting nervous, too.
（モブ）
どうしよう
僕まで緊張してきた
Spirits and Such Consultation Office
（ドアが開く音）
（男性客）すいませ～ん
Pardon me.
Oh, hello there! Sorry about the mess.
（霊幻）
あ～ どうもどうも
散らかってて すみません
そちらにお掛けください
Please have a seat right over there.
Serizawa, get our guest some tea.
芹沢 お茶をお出しして
T-Tea? I-I'm sorry,
I've never made tea before...
（芹沢）
お… お茶？
す… すみません 入れたことが…
We're doomed.
（エクボ）
ダメだ こりゃ